Juan Pablo Lezcano Full Stack Developer

≥ jplezcano75@gmail.com 📞 16043889559 • Pemberton, BC. Canada.

JuanPiPem in juan-pablo-lezcano

₽ Profile

I'm a positive, open-minded individual who thrives on teamwork. As a certified Full Stack Developer, I've been actively involved in multiple projects over the past year. My expertise encompasses a range of technologies.

These projects were collaborative efforts, where I worked closely with teams employing agile methodologies.

Experience

Full Stack Developer - Box Delivery, Plataforma5

01/2024 - 03/2024

Remote

A mobile platform, powered by React technology, aimed at courier services, allowing a company to geolocate couriers and assign them daily packages.

Front End Dev. - Mi Turno Web, Plataforma5

11/2023 - 11/2023

Web app for scheduling appointments across multiple company branches. Scrum methodology with weekly sprints and daily meetings. Remote

Education

Full Stack Developer, *Plataforma5* □

09/2023 - 12/2023

JavaScript boot camp with more than 1000 hours of coursework, where I engaged in pair programming and gained hands-on experience with Scrum and Trello for efficient management of project tasks.

Responsive Web Design, FreeCodeCamp □

2022

Remote

Learn HTML and CSS for visually appealing, responsive web design. Discover Flexbox and CSS Grid for versatile layouts.

Canada

Skills

JavaScript | Node.js | Espress | TypeScript | SQL | PSQL | React | Next | JWT | HTML/CSS | Sass | Redux | Tailwindcss | Git | GitHub | Postman | Trello

Languages

English Spanish Full working proficiency (C2) Native